<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<strings>
  <schematron.title>HNAP validation rules - multilingual</schematron.title>

  <Metadata>Metadata Information</Metadata>
  <DataIdentification>Data Identification</DataIdentification>
  <Distribution>Distribution</Distribution>

  <MetadataStandardName>Value is not valid for Metadata Standard Name, should be 'North American Profile of ISO 19115:2003 - Geographic information - Metadata' in english and 'Profil nord-américain de la norme ISO 19115:2003 - Information géographique - Métadonnées' in french</MetadataStandardName>
  <OrganisationNameThesaurus>Thesaurus organization name is required in both languages</OrganisationNameThesaurus>
  <MapServicesLanguage>For online resources map services (OGC:WMS, Esri REST: Map Service protocols) the language attribute is required</MapServicesLanguage>

  <MetadataTitle>Title is required in both languages</MetadataTitle>
  <MetadataAbstract>Abstract is required in both languages</MetadataAbstract>

  <ContactGovEnglish>English value for Contact - Organisation name in 'Goverment of Canada' should have a valid title value. See http://www.tbs-sct.gc.ca/fip-pcim/reg-eng.asp.</ContactGovEnglish>
  <ContactGovFrench>French value for Contact - Organisation name in 'Goverment of Canada' should have a valid title value. See http://www.tbs-sct.gc.ca/fip-pcim/reg-eng.asp.</ContactGovFrench>
  <ContactGovAllowedEnglish>English value for Contact - Organisation name must be one of: </ContactGovAllowedEnglish>
  <ContactGovAllowedFrench>French value for Contact - Organisation name must be one of: </ContactGovAllowedFrench>

  <CitedResponsibleContactGovEnglish>English value for Cited Responsible Contact - Organisation name in 'Goverment of Canada' should have a valid title value. See http://www.tbs-sct.gc.ca/fip-pcim/reg-eng.asp.</CitedResponsibleContactGovEnglish>
  <CitedResponsibleContactGovFrench>French value for Cited Responsible Contact - Organisation name in 'Goverment of Canada' should have a valid title value. See http://www.tbs-sct.gc.ca/fip-pcim/reg-eng.asp.</CitedResponsibleContactGovFrench>
  <CitedResponsibleContactGovAllowedEnglish>English value for Cited Responsible Contact - Organisation name must be one of: </CitedResponsibleContactGovAllowedEnglish>
  <CitedResponsibleContactGovAllowedFrench>French value for Cited Responsible Contact - Organisation name must be one of: </CitedResponsibleContactGovAllowedFrench>

  <DistributorGovEnglish>English value for Distributor Contact - Organisation name in 'Goverment of Canada' should have a valid title value. See http://www.tbs-sct.gc.ca/fip-pcim/reg-eng.asp.</DistributorGovEnglish>
  <DistributorGovFrench>French value for Distributor Contact - Organisation name in 'Goverment of Canada' should have a valid title value. See http://www.tbs-sct.gc.ca/fip-pcim/reg-eng.asp.</DistributorGovFrench>
  <DistributorGovAllowedEnglish>English value for Distributor Contact - Organisation name must be one of: </DistributorGovAllowedEnglish>
  <DistributorGovAllowedFrench>French value for Distributor Contact - Organisation name must be one of: </DistributorGovAllowedFrench>

  <OpenLicenseEnglish>An English supported license is required. Accepted values: </OpenLicenseEnglish>
  <OpenLicenseFrench>A French supported license is required. Accepted values: </OpenLicenseFrench>
  <SupplementalInfo>Supplemental Information should be empty or filled in both languages</SupplementalInfo>
  <Keyword>Keyword is required in both languages</Keyword>

  <OtherConstraintsNote2>Note (Other Constraints) is required in both languages</OtherConstraintsNote2>

  <ResourceName>Online resource name is required in both language</ResourceName>
  <ResourceDescription>Online resource description is not valid. The format should be: ContentType;Format;Lang</ResourceDescription>
  <ResourceDescriptionContentTypeEnglish>English online resource description content type is not valid. Valid English values are: </ResourceDescriptionContentTypeEnglish>
  <ResourceDescriptionContentTypeFrench>French online resource description content type is not valid. Valid French values are: </ResourceDescriptionContentTypeFrench>
  <ResourceDescriptionFormat>Online resource description format is not valid. Valid values are:</ResourceDescriptionFormat>
  <ResourceDescriptionLanguage>Online resource description language is not valid. Should be a comma separated values of ISO-LANG-3 codes</ResourceDescriptionLanguage>
  <SecurityLevel>Security User Note is not valid. Valid values are:</SecurityLevel>
  <SecurityNoteBothLangRequired>Value is required for Security User Note in both languages</SecurityNoteBothLangRequired>
  <SecurityNoteMismatchedBothLang>Value mismatched for Security User Note in both languages</SecurityNoteMismatchedBothLang>
  <SecurityClassificationUserNote>Security User Note is not valid for the classification code selected. Valid values are:</SecurityClassificationUserNote>
  <SecurityClassificationUserNoteEmpty>Security User Note should be empty for the classification code selected</SecurityClassificationUserNoteEmpty>
  <OtherConstraintsNote>If you indicate 'Other Restrictions' in the 'Access Constraints' or 'Use Constraints' fields, the other constraints for accessing or using the resource should be explained here.</OtherConstraintsNote>
  <UseLimitation>Value is required for Use Limitation in both languages</UseLimitation>

  <ContactOrganisationName>Contact - Organization name is required in both languages</ContactOrganisationName>
  <CitedResponsiblePartyOrganisationName>Cited Responsible Party - Organization name is required in both languages</CitedResponsiblePartyOrganisationName>
  <DistributorOrganisationName>Distributor - Organization name is required in both languages</DistributorOrganisationName>

  <FileDescription>GraphicOverlay (thumbnail) - File Description should be empty or filled in English and French</FileDescription>

  <ContactPositionName>Contact - Position Name should be empty or filled in English and French</ContactPositionName>
  <CitedResponsiblePartyPositionName>Cited Responsible Party - Position Name should be empty or filled in English and French</CitedResponsiblePartyPositionName>
  <DistributorPositionName>Distributor - Position Name should be empty or filled in English and French</DistributorPositionName>

  <ContactElectronicMail>Contact - Electronic mail address is required in both languages</ContactElectronicMail>
  <CitedResponsiblePartyElectronicMail>Cited Responsible Party - Electronic mail address is required in both languages</CitedResponsiblePartyElectronicMail>
  <DistributorElectronicMail>Distributor - Electronic mail address is required in both languages</DistributorElectronicMail>

  <ContactHoursOfService>Contact - Hours of service should be empty or filled in English and French</ContactHoursOfService>
  <CitedResponsiblePartyHoursOfService>Cited Responsible Party - Hours of service should be empty or filled in English and French</CitedResponsiblePartyHoursOfService>
  <DistributorHoursOfService>Distributor - Hours of service should be empty or filled in English and French</DistributorHoursOfService>

  <ContactDeliveryPoint>Contact - Delivery Point should be empty or filled in English and French</ContactDeliveryPoint>
  <CitedResponsiblePartyDeliveryPoint>Cited Responsible Party - Delivery Point should be empty or filled in English and French</CitedResponsiblePartyDeliveryPoint>
  <DistributorDeliveryPoint>Distributor - Delivery Point should be empty or filled in English and French</DistributorDeliveryPoint>

  <ContactAdministrativeArea>Contact - Province/State should be empty or filled in English and French with a valid value</ContactAdministrativeArea>
  <CitedResponsiblePartyAdministrativeArea>Cited Responsible Party - Province/State should be empty or filled in English and French  with a valid value</CitedResponsiblePartyAdministrativeArea>
  <DistributorAdministrativeArea>Distributor - Province/State should be empty or filled in English and French with a valid value</DistributorAdministrativeArea>

  <ContactPhone>Contact - Phone should be empty or filled in English and French</ContactPhone>
  <CitedResponsiblePartyPhone>Cited Responsible Party - Phone should be empty or filled in English and French</CitedResponsiblePartyPhone>
  <DistributorPhone>Distributor - Phone should be empty or filled in English and French</DistributorPhone>

  <ECCountry>Country should have a value as defined in the ISO 3166 code list. See https://www.iso.org/obp/ui/#search/code/</ECCountry>
  <ECThesaurusTitle>Thesaurus title is required</ECThesaurusTitle>
  <ECThesaurusPubDate>Thesaurus publication date is required</ECThesaurusPubDate>
  <ECThesaurusCreDate>Thesaurus creation date is required</ECThesaurusCreDate>
  <ECThesaurusOrg>Thesaurus cited responsible party organisation is required</ECThesaurusOrg>
  <ECThesaurusRole>Thesaurus cited responsible party role is required</ECThesaurusRole>
  <ECThesaurusEmail>Thesaurus cited responsible party email is required</ECThesaurusEmail>

  <ElectronicMailFormat>Electronic mail address format is invalid (for example abc@abc.com)</ElectronicMailFormat>
</strings>
